Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
These children have been completely drained of magic.
It's been taken, and I don't know if they can ever regain it.
What kind of monster are you?
Meanwhile, I'll see what I can do about this little runt over here.
You won't get away with this. I will make you pay!
MUSIC
PARTICULAR
Run to the stage
渇くほど願い
水が糸を伝え
誰かに叶う
混乱なせ
Go. Joe.
What's it just like?
Yeah,
only moving in
digamos.
A sudden love
to listen
to fill
you
that
and
开
.
Tell me
how
to
block
The
hero
says
no
Nope,
Dr Georgia
Let's go over
If so,共に見よう
今は黒に染めよう
こんなふざけた時代
Let's go over
今日の間に僕ら並び立って
今から扉を開くから
Let's go over
Huh, the Black Bull's headquarters are closer to Naon than any of the other Magic Knight squads
So why are they taking so long to respond to the alert?
Huh, huh
Then again, who knows what a bunch of misfit crazies like them might be up to in the middle of the night
Is anyone here?
We have a request for backup
Right, well, I guess I'll just head back then
I'm not running scared or anything
More like the Black Bull's ran off because they were afraid of me
I know
I'll head for the Blue Rose Knights
That gorgeous garden of girls
Farewell, creepy old mansion
Seke's got a date with some lovely ladies
These
Beautiful moon out tonight
Hi, I'm Gordon
But you can call me Donnie
No, please stop
I swear I'm not trespassing
Hey, I think I recognize you
You're Seke burns on
So for entering mantises
Would you like to be friends with me?
I'm going to die
That is the face of a man who wants to kill me
Shall I put the cat on for some tea?
Back, get back
No, don't kill me
Another psycho
I gotta get out of here
Shut up
Jeez
Just when a guy's getting some quality shut eye
It's ohaha this and ohaha that
Do you have any idea what time it is?
The Black Bull's captain
My apologies for the late hour
I have a backup request for the
Who the hell are you?
Hey, you're not here to collect my bar tab, are you?
Bar tab?
No, I'm not
I was sent with an alert from the Magic Knight headquarters
I've never been to any Magic Knight bar
No, it's Neon Village
I already paid my tab in Neon
Can we forget about paying up for a second?
You think I'm going to pay twice?
So, do you take any sugar?
What is the deal with this squad?
Why didn't I go to the Blue Rose Knights when I had the chance?
Hey, quit zoning out like a moron and take him down!
these things again mirror magic now reflect refrain
are you done now
then die feeble little rich no get away
i got you now he's trapped no his mirror's been silenced don't worry gosh i'll save you
save me if you're trying to show off for marie it won't work now is the time for your stubbornness
shut up i have everything under control rather we do knees behind you
how are there two mirror magic real double
my real double spell summons a clone from the mirror world into this one
i cast it quickly right before you used your snow magic to capture me
so cool your magic is officially awesome gosh the smaller of the two has tremendous magic power
enough to make snowfall over an entire village but ghost's power is just as great and he's always
excelled when it comes to fighting with magic he truly is strong if only he weren't such an ill-mannered
thug don't just lay there like a useless lump knees get up and fight damn it i can't move there's got to be
something oh that's it i could try how could you do something so screwed up you stole their magic can you
imagine if somebody had taken yours
except they didn't know did they if a bunch of snot-nosed brats lose their magic that's their
problem not mine the pain you're in is nothing compared to what you deserve you will find a way to fix this
that's enough don't waste your energy on him he's not worth the effort
what's important right now is taking care of the children hey tell us how to make their magic
return yes i'll tell you whatever you want to know if you'll just let me go it's time to quit
stalling you're scum all right through and through asta use your sword to break the spell that's on the
children first and you don't try anything funny yeah well i'm kind of tied up at the moment so
i'm kind of tied up at the moment so
mud magic mud man
where am i mommy daddy
sister there there it will be all right children
asta everything's gonna be fine don't worry hurry up and heal marie's injuries you old cow
i was going to anyway you uncivilized oaf flame recovery magic sacred healing light
hey you brats in the middle there marie should have the best spot so move over and make room it's okay i
i don't care where i sit that's my marie with the kindness of an angel and an angel deserves the
best the spell will work the same no matter where she is i've got some dried pot potatoes here marie
they'll perk you right up keep that garbage away from my sister hey it's my hometown specialty
aster weren't you raised at the church in harsh village yeah how did you know
well as it happens sister lily once came to my church to train she told me all about a young
orphan who was in her care seriously you actually know sister lily one of the sweetest young ladies
i've ever met i know right wait what exactly did she tell you was it good she told me that you were
little and noisy of course that wasn't the only thing she said
once this is done i'll move on to the windows easy now you'll wear yourself out if you work this
hard from day one sister this is nothing i promise i know someone who works so hard he puts my efforts
to shame oh there's a boy back in hodge who can't use magic at all but still spends every day
training in hopes of becoming the wizard king you must be joking he can't even get into a magic night
squad if he doesn't have magic probably not but if you told him to give up he'd say not yet i'm not
done so maybe he will now i'm saying it too get some rest not yet i'm not done
she also told me that you're a hard worker who doesn't give up no matter what obstacles he faces
a boy with a strong heart who makes her proud every day and now i can see that all of your
hard work has paid off yeah and i'm not done i'm gonna be the wizard king someday too now about that
i'm not giving up sister lily i'm not giving up on you either so please please please please
please marry me you're the one who hit her marie told me that crime can only be paid for with your
life that's enough gosh i'm fine i'll heal up in everything please don't hurt him anymore can't you
just forgive him not a chance if someone poses a threat to my beloved marie i will show no mercy
we need to focus on getting that magic back not petty vengeance oh tell me why did the two of you do
this these children are the hope of our kingdom the three leaf sprouts upon which our future depends
i didn't want this i just wanted to make some new friends it hurts please borrow tell me what i should
do well for a start you could quit whining like a little brat damn damn damn it's not fair why did this
have to happen to me it's all her fault i thought we were gonna make a fortune but it was a trick the whole
time come on show your stupid face oh that sounds like finally pretty slow for someone who can use
special magic we hit a snack think i could get a little help here oh i am so sick of your whining
but it looks like you brought me a present so i'll let it slide
awesome the eye of the midnight sun i didn't expect to see you again so soon it's the crazy lady
what something's going down in neon and you didn't think you should mention it sooner you idiot
but i did try to tell you no excuses so they need backup do they
no one's ever really sure what these two weirdos are thinking guess i should go except i don't wanna
how did these three even make it into the magic knights
everyone please remain calm head to the church for now where are they i miss them it'll be okay
they'll be home soon i'm certain they may not look it but asta and gauche are both really strong
and we'll be getting back up from headquarters too yeah really
you kids want to help with dinner sure
we are getting back up aren't we what's this i came when the transmission tool alerted me
but you haven't gathered much magic yeah well it's all their fault
it doesn't really matter anymore stay here children no one move
is it their master the terrorist group who attacked the capital yeah it's the same people
you're the one my marie was in danger because of you you're dead chill magic
i'm trying to have a touching reunion here and you're messing it up
maybe i should keep all of you dissection party what sort of sinister magic is that be careful
it's real strong it's real strong i heard she blocked the captain of the silver eagles attack
oh
silly asta your anti-magic attacks can't do much if they don't connect
what about this mirror magic reflect refrain
she's warping the beams hey it's nice magic and all but if it just
refracts inside mr. Salomon here it's not exactly effective maybe you'd have
better luck if you tried something stronger
there you are my pretty one you look like such an ordinary human
but you're not you're special
that hurts and it's freaky oh your blood's ordinary enough now next up i need a fingernail sample
flame magic brilliant flame cross
you might as well back off you're not taking him you really shouldn't get in my way
that was awesome hey thanks wow you're really powerful huh don't underestimate theresa the
crimson she leopard once a magic knight always a magic knight
oh didn't see that one coming
you were a magic knight crimson she leopard so you know captain fuegolion little fuego of course
little fuego back when i was stationed at court i was in charge of his education
your mana is all over the place oh right your foes won't hesitate in battle you must learn to focus
and remain calm at all times ma'am he was a real mess back then but he turned out all right
i cannot picture that
i don't know if you heard about what happened to captain fuegolion's sister
they will yes i know and we will capture them think you can help me out you old bat
what are you doing over there you boorish brute shut up old crone
so it's three against one then i'm not liking these odds hey over here if i was free i could use my mud
magic to help you cut me loose it'll be a win-win you can do something right well yeah there is a way
to get you out but are you really sure you want me to of course i'm sure whatever it takes come on
okay why not you're sure yes really sure i said yes just do it hey what are you two muttering about
over there hurry up would you get me out of these and pay me like we agreed and i'll help you take
down all three of them yeah right as soon as i'm free and i've got my money i'm out of here all right
all right then in that case here what the
what's happening what's she do
oh he's becoming some sort of monster his magic swelling up and spilling out
whoopsie that didn't work i mean you can move and you've got scads of magic power now
wouldn't you be cool except for the whole not being human thing
ghost aster keep the children safe on it
we're leaving marie hold on we can't go all of the other kids are still down there
forget about them the only thing that matters is getting you away from that monster
what that fool
i'm not going to let you go this time
big brother
you
Oh, oh...
You can't tell it
For when theём plants will scare you
oh
All right, I've delivered the backup request for headquarters, so now I can get out of here.
This hideout, it's like a maze.
Where?
Who the heck are you?
Why are you following me?
What room is this?
I should be safe in here.
Please, I'm way too young to die.
How the heck do I get out of here?
Mirror, mirror on the wall.
Who's the... never mind.
Marie's the cutest.
I don't need a mirror to tell me that.
Black Clover, page 33.
To help somebody someday.
My magic is protecting Marie.